Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual materials, 1977-2012; Series VII; 1.63; (3 boxes)
  - Interview for Jack Spicer bio and miscellaneous audiocassettes, 112; 1 (Box 85)
    - Martin Block interviewed by Kevin Killian, L.A., 1993 December 18; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364284)
    - New Design Gallery reading, Robin Blaser, Jack Spicer, Stan Persky, 1965 June; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364292)
    - Jack Langan Interview, 1992 July 17; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364300)
    - Basil King interviewed, Brooklyn, 1992 September 4; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364318)
    - Jack Spicer, "Poetry & Politics", 1965 July 14; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364326)
      Introduction by Professor Thomas Parkinson, Poetry Conference, Berkeley
    - Fran Herndon interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1997 February 1; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364334)
    - Sam Hardin interviewed by Kevin Killian, Berkeley (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1993 January 31; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364342)
    - Sam Hardin Interview (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1993 January 31; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364466)
    - Gladys Hindmarch, Neap Hoover & Leni Hoover interviewed by Terry Ludwar, Vancouver, 1991 July 1; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364359)
    - J. A. Ryan interviewed by KK, 1993 June 19; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364367)
    - John Allen Ryan interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, side 3, 1992 May 31; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364375)
    - James Schevill interview, Berkeley, 1992 October 24; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364383)
    - Stuart Loomis interviewed by KK, San Francisco, 1995 July 9; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364391)
    - Latif Harris interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1996 July 9; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364409)
    - Barbara Nicholls tape, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364417)
    - Summer Days I, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364425)
    - American Poetry Archive, #45 copy, George Stanley, Jack Gilbert, Sue Rosen, 1957 June 10; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364433)
    - Wesley Day, 2nd interview, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364441)
    - Earl McGrath interviewed by Kevin Killian, Beverly Hills, CA, 1991 September 21; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364458)
    - Spicer Vancouver Lecture #1, Side 5 and 6, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363773)
    - Spicer Vancouver Lecture #1, Side 1 and 2, 1965 June 13; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099363781)
    - Jack Spicer Vancouver Lecture #1, tape 2, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364474)
    - Larry Kearney interview, 1995 November 25; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364482)
    - "Cool Side" (V-Day Ex) / Birthday tape, Steve Dickison (Quincey in Letters of Mina Harker) made for Dodie, late 1980s; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364490)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364508)
    - Dannil - Girl and Extras, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364078)
    - Robin Blaser interviewed by Kevin Killian, Vancouver, side 2 and 3, 1992 May 22; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364516)
    - Stephanie Tedusco, 1994 August 2; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364524)
    - The Chance Band, Live!, 1996 November 10; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364532)
      Live at Whiskey Pete's Casino for the Saturday night party, Nevada
    - Dick Bratset interviewed by Kevin Killian, San Francisco, 1993 October 3; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364540)
    - Wayne Burns interviewed by Kevin Killian, Seattle, Washington, 1993 April 27; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364557)
    - Wesley Day Interview, sides 1 & 2 (1 of 2 audiocassettes), 1991 October 25; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364565)
    - Wesley Day Interview, sides 3 & 4 (2 of 2 audiocassettes), 1991 October 25; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364573)
    - Arthur Kloth A K, 1990 November 4; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364581)
    - Jack Spicer 2, undated; 1 (Box 85, Item barcode 39002099364599)
- Electronic media, 1991-2008; Series VIII; .42; (1 box)
  - DHP, "Dorian Jason Arik" and "Dorian Misfit", 2002–2003; 2 (Box 86)
  - 4 DVDs about Kylie Minogue, 2008, undated; 4 (Box 86)
    4 DVD-rs labelled as follows: "The Kylie Show and misc live performances", Kylie X 2008 (ntsc)", "Kylie Minogue White Diamond", and "An Audience with Kylie Minogue"
  - Killian/Guest Medley, undated; 2 (Box 86)
  - CD Images Killian Clifford Irving Show, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Window Window "happy revolution, first last only", undated; 1 (Box 86)
    Disk labelled: "Window Window for Dodie Song # For" on one side. Back of Jewel Case labelled "The Extended (Belated) Feb. 14th Remix"
  - May 8 2005 Thomas and Lisa, 2005 May 08; 1 (Box 86)
  - DHP, "Dorian Kade" and "Dorian Jason Arik", 2002–2007; 2 (Box 86)
  - Killian, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Fred's Excerpt pages 39-43 Promised Lans Part III, circa 1993; 1 (Box 86)
    1 3 1/4" disk
  - Kathy Lou Schultz, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Edmund White by Kevin Killian, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Angela Bowie "This is My Life", undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - 12 min DVD of BIG MIX from Yoshis, San Francisco, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Digital Photo Album, undated; 1; photo CD (Box 86)
  - Philip, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Kiki 2, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - Kiki Show, undated; 1 (Box 86)
  - CDs related to Jack Spicer, 1991, undated; 2 (Box 86)
    2 cds labelled "Kat Onoma 'Billy the Kid' 1992" and "The Beat Suite Steve Lacy and Jack Spicer reading excerpts from 'Holy Grail' and 'Billy the Kid'"
  - Bookworm Prod/Host: Michael Silverblatt featuring: Dodie Bellamy, 2004 October 04; 1 (Box 86)